{"data":[{"question":"Frank Robinson gave the name Coca Cola to the drink.-> The name Coca Cola .................... to the drink by Frank Robinson.\n","answer":"was given","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"People eat thirty-five million hamburgers every day.     ->Thirty-five million hamburgers .....................every day.\n","answer":"are eaten","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Previously women thought tobacco smelly.     -> Tobacco ........................... smelly by women.\n","answer":"was previously thought","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Industrial revolution helped to develop new technologies.     -> New technologies ............................... to develop by industrial revolution.\n","answer":"were helped","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Most young people like chewing gum.     -> Chewing gum ......................... by most young people.\n","answer":"is liked","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Where did they invent gun-powder?     -> Where .......................... gun-powder invented?\n","answer":"was","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"How do you make this delicious meal?     -> How ..................................this delicious meal made?\n","answer":"is","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Why does he water these plants so rarely?     -> Why .................................. so rarely?\n","answer":"are these plants watered","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"Producers sell about 1.2 billion gallons of Sprite every day.     -> About 1.2 billion gallons of Sprite ...................... every day.\n","answer":"is sold","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"},{"question":"The police didn't find the missing girl last weekend.     -> The missing girl .......................... last week by the police\n","answer":"wasn't found","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"4"}]}